letstalk.com 2013-09-26

# Privacy & Security

[](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.letstalk.com&sealid=101)Privacy Policy

 _Last Updated: 8/21/2013_

## Introduction

This privacy policy applies to www.LetsTalk.com owned and operated by LetsTalk, Inc. This privacy policy describes how LetsTalk, Inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site: www.LetsTalk.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

Letstalk.com will notify you of: 

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the Web site;
  * How the information is used;
  * With whom the information may be shared; 
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information;
  * What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Letstalk.com’s control; and
  * How you can correct or update your information.

LetsTalk, Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe's program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, www.LetsTalk.com.

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, or complaints arising from our use of your personal information, please contact us via certified mail at: LetsTalk.com National Fulfillment Center, 1001 Technology Way, Suite LT, Libertyville, IL. 60048 ATT: Customer Service Center. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe here.

## What Information We Collect and How We Use It

Non-Personally Identifiable Information

_Location Information_  
We collect location information in order to improve your shopping experience. If you shop for location-specific products such as a wireless or satellite rate plan, we ask for a zip code and record this information via a cookie so that we may display only services which are available in your area. We also save this information so that we don’t have to ask for it again on your next visit.

We also collect information about your computer, including without limitation hardware, software and configuration information, your IP address, operating system, browser type, domain name of your Internet service provider, URL, access times and/or referring Web site address. We use this information to evaluate and track your order, help administer our Web site, examine overall traffic trends and to help improve our site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. We also use this information to improve the design and content of our Web site, personalize your Internet experience, analyze service usage, track user activity and minimize fraud.

_Cookies_  
Cookies are used by your computer's browser to store your preferences. We use both session and persistent cookies. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or personally identifiable information. In addition, some of our advertisers and business partners or affiliates may use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies and their use is not covered by this Privacy Policy. They may also employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We do tie the information gathered to our Customers’ or Users’ personally identifiable information.

_Flash LSOs_  
We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences such as volume control or high game score, or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use Flash cookies to collect and store information.

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here:

[http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118 ](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118)

_Tracking Pixels_  
This site makes use of a technology designed to enhance your browsing experience and to monitor and enhance the effectiveness of marketing activities conducted by us and/or our business partners or affiliates. The technology makes use of a small and transparent Java. Aggregate reporting information is collected and made available to us and/or our business partners or affiliates. No personal or personally identifiable information is gathered or used in this process.

_Online Preference Marketing_  
We use third party advertising companies and advertising networks, including without limitation Microsoft and AudienceScience, to serve targeted behavioral and multi-site advertisements to you on our behalf when you visit our Web site. They do this by researching and collecting Web site usage and behavioral data through the use of cookies, monitoring technologies and Web beacons to provide targeted advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you on our, and other, Web sites. These companies do not use your personally identifiable information to provide this service. If you would like more information about this practice, or to opt-out of the collection of this information on our Web site, please visit: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>; and/or [http://privacy.microsoft.com](http://privacy.microsoft.com/).

Personally Identifiable Information

_Order Information_  
When you place an order for products or services we collect certain types of personally identifiable information required to fulfill those product and/or service order, including (1) contact information (such as name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number); (2) payment information (such as credit card number); and/or (3) ID verification information (such as credit card number, date of birth, Social Security Number, and/or Driver's License Number).

We collect ID verification information to determine your eligibility and/or process your application We, and/or the service provider, may perform an identity and/or credit check as a part of our fraud protection and order fulfillment process. In the event that your order is not approved by the service provider of your choice without a deposit, we may also submit your data to an alternate service provider who also may perform an identity and/or credit check.

If you would like to place an order but are reluctant to provide this information online, you may provide it to us by telephone during our normal business hours. For wireless products and services, telephone agents are available when the Order By Phone button is visible on one of the shopping pages of our site. Simply click on this button to speak to an agent and provide your information over the phone.

We use the contact information you provide to communicate with you, such as to send you order confirmations, respond to your inquiries and provide you with important product updates, warranty and/or safety information. In addition, we use contact information you provide to offer you additional products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. You can easily opt out of receiving marketing emails by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the e-mail. Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not share, sell, rent or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes unless you authorize us to do so.

_Forward-To-A-Friend and Refer-A-Friend_  
If you choose to use our email forwarding functionality or our referral service to tell a friend about our Web site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend the forwarded email or a one-time promotional email, as applicable. We use this information for the sole purpose of forwarding the email or sending the one-time promotional email and delete the information afterwards.

_Supplementation of Information_  
We may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect online with outside records (e.g., information from our strategic partners, service providers, or the United States Postal Service) to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

_Affiliate Sign-Up Process_  
For individuals or entities that apply to become an affiliate of Letstalk.com, you are applying to be an affiliate of Hercle™ subject to Hercle’s privacy policy available at: <http://www.hercle.com/affiliate/accounts/default1/themes/signup/Hercle_Signup/pdfs/IMS_HERCLE_Privacy_Policy.pdf>.

_Social Media_  
If you use a blog on one of our Web sites, any personally identifiable information you submit or post on such sites can be read, collected, and/or used by other users of these sites. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit on these sites.

_Surveys_  
During and/or after your visit to our Web site, we may ask you questions about our products and services and/or your shopping experience. If you submit answers to these questions, we may place your answers and your first name on our Web site to inform other customers and improve their shopping experience, but we will not list any personally identifiable information other than your first name without first receiving your approval to do so.

## Sharing of Your Information

Trusted Third Parties

Please be assured that any third parties who have access to the information you provide, including our marketing partners, agents, contractors and business partners or affiliates, have agreed to protect it in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. To fulfill your requests for products and services, we may need to share some of your personally identifiable information with the service provider from which you have requested service. More specifically, when you place an order, we will share contact and ID verification information required by the service provider. The service provider may use this information for credit approval, service activation, and from time to time, its own marketing purposes in accordance with its privacy policy. You should consult the service providers' privacy policy, as this Privacy Policy does not cover their use of your information. We may need to share your personally identifiable information with other third party service providers that assist us with online chat services, credit card processing, fraud screening and shipping in connection with your order and/or use of our site. These service providers are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. We also work closely with and may share your contact information with trusted third party business partners or affiliates to provide you with information on products and services that may be of interest to you.

Co-branded Web Sites and Offers

In addition, you can access Letstalk.com through many third party co-branded Web sites and partner marketing efforts. For example, if you see a logo on the page that says "Powered by Letstalk.com," you are on a co-branded page. Whenever you provide contact information on a co-branded page, that data may be shared with the third party site or partner through which you access Letstalk.com. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of such third parties, as their privacy policy also governs their use of your information.

Letstalk.com sometimes may offer content (e.g., promotions, affiliations, sponsorships) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable and other information that users voluntarily submit or authorize Letstalk.com to provide to accept the offer. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of such third parties, as their privacy policy also governs the maintenance and use of your information.

Links

This site may contain links to other Web sites whose information practices may be different from ours. Our Privacy Policy does not cover these third party Web sites’ uses of your information. Visitors should consult the sites' privacy notice as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

Legal Process/Disclaimer

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to or in connection with judicial or regulatory proceedings or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena or a law enforcement agency's request.

## Security

We have put in place multiple levels of physical and electronic security to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to our systems, maintain data security and securely use the information we collect. These measures include secure Web pages, VeriSign SSL certificate ensuring the privacy and security of order information, and HackerSafe certification, representing the highest security scanning standards of the U.S. government and all major credit card providers. All information submitted is protected by our secure server, which automatically encrypts your personally identifiable information so that it cannot be read while traveling over the Internet.

## Reviewing and Making Choices About the Use of Your Information

Reviewing and Updating Your Information

If you would like to review, update, correct and/or delete the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you online, simply send your request via certified mail to: LetsTalk.com National Fulfillment Center, 1001 Technology Way, Suite LT, Libertyville, IL. 60048 ATT: Customer Service Center. For wireless service customers, you may also send your request via the Customer Support feedback section in our [customer service center.](http://www.letstalk.com/about/contact1.htm) To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your personal information.

Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Choices/Opt Out

If you prefer not to receive marketing information, including emails, from us, or wish to deactivate your account information if you are no longer an active customer, simply send your request via certified mail to: LetsTalk.com National Fulfillment Center, 1001 Technology Way, Suite LT, Libertyville, IL. 60048 ATT: Customer Service Center. Please note that if you choose to opt out of marketing programs, you will continue to receive important service-related communications (e.g., order confirmation or product safety information) which is not promotional in nature. 

Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, simply send your inquiry to us via certified mail at: LetsTalk.com National Fulfillment Center, 1001 Technology Way, Suite LT, Libertyville, IL. 60048 ATT: Customer Service Center. 

## Updates and Notification of Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

## Acceptance of this Privacy Policy

By visiting this Web site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

Security

Why shopping with LetsTalk.com is safe. LetsTalk.com has implemented multiple levels of web site security to ensure a safe online shopping environment. We use a secure server, have received SSL secure server certification, practice credit card encryption, do not store Credit card verification numbers and have our site scanned monthly by an external source. 

Secure Web Server  
In keeping with the highest standards of safety, LetsTalk.com's secure server protects web pages that request or display a customer's personal information.

SSL Secure Server Digicert Certificate  
LetsTalk.com has received a Secure Server Certificate issued by Digicert ensuring that a user's order will be completely private and secure. 

Encryption  
LetsTalk.com customer credit card information is processed using the highest bit encryption available.

CVN Not Stored  
LetsTalk is contributing to preserving a safe environment for online credit card use by never storing the CVN numbers printed on credit cards.

Certified & Scanned by Ambiron  
LetTalk.com has received certification issued by Ambiron that states that the LetsTalk site is safe for online shoppers. Ambiron performs scheduled scanning every month to ensure that the LetsTalk site remains a safe shopping environment. 

In addition to technical security, we do not share data with other organizations. See our Privacy Policy.

Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, LetsTalk.com will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. We will cover this liability only if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at LetsTalk.com while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. 

For more detailed information about our security measures, contact customer service.  

Cookies  
Cookies are small text files sent to your computer when you visit certain web pages. They are stored on your computer's hard drive and keep track of various data such as what you have in your shopping cart and the zip code you have entered.

Although LetsTalk cookies cannot harm your computer and do not contain any personal or private information we understand certain users have a mistrust of them. Therefore, we recently made changes to the way our site uses them. It is no longer necessary to enable permanent cookies (if your browser allows you this level of detail), but you will need to allow session cookies.

How to enable session cookies:  
(If you do not know your browser version, click on help in your browser menu and then click the About... option) 

Microsoft Internet Explorer 7.0 or 8.0  
Click Start > Control Panel. (Note: with Windows XP Classic View, click the Windows Start button > Settings > Control Panel).  
Double-click the Internet Options icon  
Click the Privacy tab.   
Click the Advanced button.  
To edit the default settings (which do allow permanent cookies) check the box that reads "Override Automatic Cookie Handling".  
This will allow you to set First & Third Party cookie handling. (For LetsTalk.com you may set any option you want to here, including Blocking Cookies.)  
You must check the box that reads, "Always allow session cookies".  

Microsoft Internet Explorer 6.0  
Click Start > Control Panel. (Note: with Windows XP Classic View, click the Windows Start button > Settings > Control Panel).  
Click the Advanced button.  
To edit the default settings (which do allow permanent cookies) check the box that reads "Override Automatic Cookie Handling".  
This will allow you to set First & Third Party cookie handling. (For LetsTalk.com you may set any option you want to here, including Blocking Cookies.)  
You must check the box that reads, "Always allow session cookies".  

Mozilla Firefox 3.0, 3.5, 3.6  
Select Tools -> Options and click on "Privacy" in the list on the left.  
Set 'Firefox will': to Use custom settings for history.  
Check the box next to Accept cookies from sites to enable cookies, or uncheck it to disable them.  
Click OK.  

Mozilla Firefox 1.8  
Select Tools -> Options and click on "Privacy" in the list on the left.  
Select the "Cookies" tab which will expand the view for Cookies  
Beneath "Allow sites to set cookies" also check the box "for the originating website only"  
You may also change the default setting for Keep Cookies from "until they expire" -> "until I close Firefox".  
Click OK 

Chrome 8.0, 9.0, 10.0  
Click the Tools menu.  
Select Options.  
Click the Under the Hood tab.  
Click Content settings in the 'Privacy' section.  
Make sure Allow local data to be set is selected to allow both first-party and third-party cookies. For any given webpage, first-party cookies are cookies that are set by the site domain listed in the address bar. Third-party cookies come from other domain sources that have items, such as ads or images, embedded on the page. If you only want to accept first-party cookies, check the box next to Block all third-party cookies without exception.  

Safari 5.0  
Choose Preferences from the Safari menu -> Security. Select Never if you don't want to store any cookies on your computer. This may prevent you from using some websites.  
Click Always to accept and remember all cookies  
Click "Only from sites you navigate to" to prevent storing cookies that come from websites other than those you open.  
To see the cookies you have accepted, click Show Cookies. You can then remove cookies.  

All other browsers  

Please consult your documentation or online help files. 

iFrames

iFrames are frames that can be integrated anywhere into the html of a page and are less constrictive to use than traditional html frames. iFrames are used in various places on the Letstalk site. If you received an error message regarding iFrames, your browser may be configured to disallow display. MacAfee Security defaultly disables the display of iFrames. 

There is nothing unsafe or questionable regarding our use of iFrames. To have full site functionality you should enable them. If you choose to modify that setting, follow the instructions below. 

In Internet Explorer, V6  
Click tools > Security > Internet  
Click "Custom Level"  
Select "Launching programs and files in an IFRAME" > enable  

For Firefox  
In the browser window in the URL, type "about:config" > browser.frames.enabled"  
Double click it and set it true
